JACK COOKSLEY

cooksley02@gmail.com | 0478024571 | Brisbane, QLD 4000

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Bar Attendant excels in fast-paced and high-traffic environments. 5+ years of responsible alcohol serving experience. Experienced in a range of cocktails from classics to own creations. Management experience from stock taking, ordering, maintaining point of sales systems, cash handling, reconciliation, gaming machines, pool and dart competitions, promotion and sales of new products. training and managing staff

SKILLS

- Cocktails
- Craft Beer, Cider, Wine and Spirit knowledge
- Inventory
- Ordering
- Cellar control, changing beer kegs

- Mentoring
- Sales and promotion
- Stock control
- Supervisor

WORK HISTORY

Bar Attendant / Zenith Hospitality / 10.2018 - 02.2020

- Private functions- bar tending, cocktail making
- Octoberfest Brisbane Festival bar attendant, cellar hand, private function barwork

Duty Manager / Liquorland-Tauranga/Mount Maunganui NZ - Mount Maunganui, Bay of Plenty New Zealand / 07.2017 - 07.2018

- Stock take, Counting of merchandise for inventory purposes
- Completed appropriate forms to request orders and prepare licensee orders
- Ensured the security of merchandise through constant visual and physical surveillance
- Opening and closure of outlet
- Acting Manager when General Manager absent

Bar Attendant / Burrito Brothers - Tauranga, Bay of Plenty New zealand / 06.2017 - 09.2017

 Cocktail bar attendant in a busy award winning, Mexican themed restaurant

Bar Manager / Talisman Hotel - Katikati, Bay of Plenty New Zealand / 05.2016 - 07.2017

- Bartending and Gaming Supervisor at a local hotel, public bar and cocktail bar in 100 seat restaurant
- Preparing alcoholic or non-alcoholic beverages for patrons
- Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving snacks and drinks
- Assessing customers' needs and preferences and making recommendations
- Drinks and Cocktail development, creation of signature cocktails and bitters
- Mentoring and Training other staff members, bar service and gaming machines
- Stock control- Stocktake, ordering, entering invoices, compiling reports for the hotel manager
- Gaming Machines- Reconciliation of takings

Cellar Hand / Morton Estate Winery - Katikati, New Zealand / 10.2014 - 01.2016

 Winery bottling line- bottling, labelling, stacking and riddling, Cleaning and general winery maintenance

Night Fill / Countdown Supermarket - Katikati, Bay of Plenty New Zealand / 01.2012 - 01.2014

- Restocking supermarket items, Maintaining displays
- Responsible for liquor department restocking and display

EDUCATION

2010

- Batchelor of Computer Science- QUT-Currently under study
- NCEA
- IT Certificate 3. CCNA
- RSA- QLD-Current
- Managers Certificate- LCQ NZ-Current